♪No matter how far the road is, don’t be afraid♪
♪길이 아무리 멀더라도 두려워하지 마세요♪
♪Love is gentle and caring♪
♪사랑은 부드럽고 배려심이 깊습니다♪
♪Those wounds will definitely scab over♪
♪그 상처는 반드시 딱지가 될 거야♪
♪Everything gathers into the flower of time♪
♪모든 것은 시간의 꽃으로 모인다♪
♪ Someone will pick it up for you eventually ♪
♪결국 누군가가 당신을 대신해 가져갈 거예요♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 가세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닐 거예요♪
♪Conversation with time♪
♪시간과 함께 이야기 나누기♪
♪The light falls gently, just take it as her answer♪
♪빛이 살며시 내리는 걸 그녀의 대답이라고 생각해♪
♪May you have him in the sea of ​​people♪
♪그를 사람들의 바다 속에 두시기를 바랍니다 ♪
♪Live a simple and peaceful life♪
♪ 간단하고 평화로운 삶을 살아보세요♪
♪Understand that life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있다는 것을 이해하세요♪
♪But, you still love♪
♪하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​사랑해요♪
♪This winter and summer♪
♪이번 겨울과 여름♪
[Love is the panacea] [Episode 9]
[사랑은 만병통치약] [9회]
[2022 Sichuan Province Characteristic Support Artworks]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 지원 예술 작품 소개 ]
[Diadaptasi dari novel "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
[Diadaptasi dari 소설 "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
It's enough.
이미 충분합니다.
From nothing to something.
아무것도 아닌 것에서.
this.
이 하나.
He paid it.
그는 지불했습니다.
OK
좋은.
how much does it cost?
비용은 얼마입니까?
It's $280.
280달러입니다.
Your boyfriend is really nice.
네 남자친구는 정말 좋은 사람이야.
No, that's not how our relationship works.
아니, 우리 관계는 그런 게 아니야.
[Cheap mobile phone store]
[ 저렴한 휴대폰 매장 ]
My wife, where are we going now?
아내여, 우리는 지금 어디로 가는 걸까요?
In the future, if you don’t understand French,
앞으로는 프랑스어를 모른다면
Don't just nod.
고개만 끄덕이지 마세요.
Don't cause unnecessary misunderstandings.
불필요한 오해를 불러일으키지 마세요 .
you mean
네 말 뜻은
When you just bought a mobile phone?
지금 휴대폰을 살 때?
What misunderstanding did I make?
내가 무슨 오해를 한 걸까요?
No.
아무것도 없습니다.
Why?
왜?
Borrow it.
짧게 빌리세요.
【New contact】 【Gu Shuai】
[새연락인] [잘생긴구]
already.
이미.
Handsome?
멋있는?
This is not correct.
이것은 정확하지 않습니다.
Why didn't I realize you were so narcissistic before ?
왜 전에는 당신이 그렇게 자기애적이라는 걸 몰랐나요 ?
Brother Gu is still handsome
그래도 구오빠는 잘생겼다.
I set up my number
내 번호는 내가 정했어
Be your emergency contact.
비상연락처로 해주세요.
In the future, no matter when,
앞으로도, 언제라도,
As long as you face difficulties
당신이 어려움에 직면하는 한
You can definitely find me by dialing this number.
이 번호로 전화하시면 확실히 저를 찾으실 수 있습니다 .
Aura.
후광.
Hello, emergency contact.
안녕하세요 비상연락처입니다.
There is someone beside me now
지금 내 옆에는 한 사람이 있다
Very shameless.
매우 뻔뻔합니다.
Can you help me take him away?
그를 데려가는 것을 도와주실 수 있나요?
I obey your orders.
나는 당신의 명령을 따릅니다.
Where is Boss Su going?
수사장은 어디로 가고 싶어하나요?
excuse me.
실례합니다.
Stop fighting.
다시 치지 마십시오.
It looks like he stabbed you.
당신을 찌른 건 그 사람인 것 같군요.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Stop fighting.
다시 치지 마십시오.
help.
돕다.
Maybe his spleen has ruptured and we have to get him to the hospital immediately.
비장이 터졌을 수도 있으니 즉시 병원으로 데려가야 합니다.
Use my wheelchair.
내 휠체어를 사용하세요.
OK
좋은.
Why are you silent?
너희들은 왜 침묵하는가?
Come and help.
도와주세요.
If he dies, you are responsible.
그 사람이 죽으면 책임은 당신에게 있습니다.
Come help quickly.
서둘러서 도와주세요.
If something goes wrong, you have to take responsibility.
문제가 있으면 책임을 져야 합니다.
quickly!
빠른!
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Just stay here, don't go anywhere.
그냥 여기 있어라. 아무 데도 가지 말고.
wait for me.
날 기다려.
Aura.
후광.
Call Dr. Xu.
Xu 박사에게 전화하세요.
Dr. Gu will send the injured to the hospital.
구 박사는 피해자를 병원으로 데려갈 예정이다.
boss.
보스.
quickly.
빠른.
just me.
나만.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
boss.
보스.
The emergency room received a call from translator Su.
응급실은 수 번역가의 전화를 받았습니다 .
The operating room is ready.
수술실이 준비되었습니다.
Call the police first.
먼저 경찰에 신고하세요.
This victim is a human trafficker.
이 피해자는 인신매매범입니다.
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
Boss, where are you going?
사장님, 또 어디로 가시나요?
Su Weian is still waiting for me.
Su Wei'an은 여전히 ​​나를 기다리고 있습니다.
wheelchair. boss.
휠체어. 사장.
Kursi roda Su Wei'an.
Kursi Roda Su Wei'an.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Su Wei'an!
수웨이안!
♪Rain hits the edge of the blue sea♪
♪푸른 바다 가장자리에 비가 내린다♪
♪It’s wet again♪
♪조수는 또 뭐야♪
♪Love is like the power that kills moths♪
♪사랑은 나방을 파괴하는 힘과 같습니다 ♪
♪Find yourself in the light♪
♪빛 속에서 나 자신을 발견하기♪
♪In the long dark night♪
♪밤의 긴 어둠 속에서♪
♪Miscalculated the burning flame♪
♪타오르는 불을 잘못 계산했습니다♪
♪Sebagai Bintang-bintang♪
♪세바가이 빈탕빈탕♪
♪Chenggu naive♪
♪성구 순진함♪
♪A little closer♪
♪한발짝 더 가까이♪
♪Burning all afternoon♪
♪이미 오후 내내 불타고 있어요♪
♪Too afraid of separation♪
♪이별이 너무 무서워요♪
♪Confirm one by one♪
♪하나하나 확인♪
♪In fact it turned into a wound♪
♪실은 상처가 되었어요♪
♪Must prove he is serious♪
♪ 그의 진지함을 증명해야 해♪
let's go.
갑시다.
very good.
매우 좋은.
He also secretly took photos of me.
아직도 몰래 사진을 찍고 있어요.
What are you filming secretly?
몰래 무슨 사진을 찍는 걸까요?
I take photos in public.
공개적으로 사진을 찍었습니다.
Where is my wheelchair?
내 휠체어는 어디에 있나요?
I...I forgot to bring it.
나... 가져오는 걸 깜빡했어요.
So, how do I get home?
그럼 집에 어떻게 가나요?
I'll take you to the hospital.
내가 당신을 병원으로 데려갈게요.
Did you do this on purpose?
일부러 그랬지, 그렇지?
Now you know how to hold your breath?
이제 숨을 참는 방법을 아시나요?
No.
아니요.
Don't talk nonsense, I'm not serious.
함부로 말하지 마세요. 나 안 무거워요.
I still feel
나는 아직도 생각한다
you will care
당신은 신경 쓸 것입니다
Are my hands tired from holding you?
내 손이 피곤한지 너를 안고 있으면
All the way.
끝까지 이렇게.
So, are you tired?
그래서 피곤해요?
Year.
연령.
Because you are too heavy.
왜냐하면 당신은 너무 무거우니까요.
Why do I think you should practice?
왜 연습을 해야 할 것 같은 느낌이 드는 걸까요 ?
Can you?
할 수 있나요?
I mean,
내 말은,
I will eat less next time.
다음에는 덜 먹을 거예요.
There is no need for this.
그럴 필요는 없습니다.
patient name
환자의 이름
You should eat more,
더 먹어야지,
and recover as soon as possible.
그리고 최대한 빨리 회복하세요.
Don't bother the doctor too often.
의사를 자주 괴롭히지 마십시오.
Happy eating.
즐거운 식사.
Isn't it a little late for you?
좀 늦지 않았어?
Are you learning French now?
지금 프랑스어를 배우려고?
Then please ask Teacher Su to teach you the key points.
그렇다면 수 선생님께 요점을 가르쳐 주세요.
simple.
쉬운.
Now is Teacher Su’s online teaching time.
이제 수 선생님의 온라인 강의 시간입니다 .
OK
좋은.
cough.
기침.
Retina.
망막.
Heart.
마음.
Boy friend.
남자 친구.
rib cage.
갈비 살.
Teacher Su.
수 선생님.
This last sentence,
이 마지막 말은,
It means boyfriend.
남자친구라는 뜻이에요.
Do you know what that means?
너는이 의미를 아니?
So, are you still nodding casually in the mobile phone store?
그럼 아직도 핸드폰 가게에서 무심코 고개를 끄덕이고 계시나요?
of.
의.
Why am I nodding carelessly?
왜 무심코 고개를 끄덕여야 하는 걸까?
[Friendship RS]
[우정RS]
Your recovery is going pretty well.
당신의 회복은 꽤 좋습니다.
Dokter Xu.
쑤 독터.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
There is still a little less blood.
그래도 피가 좀 덜 나네요.
I prescribed iron supplements for you.
나는 당신에게 철분 보충제를 처방했습니다.
Are you taking iron supplements again?
또 철분제?
Did anyone give you any medicine?
누군가 당신에게 그것을 처방해 주었나요?
No.
아니요.
Oh, yes, Dr. Xu.
아, 그래요, Xu 박사님.
I feel better.
나는 훨씬 나아졌습니다.
Give me the data you want translated.
번역하고 싶은 데이터를 주세요 .
Now I start translating.
이제 번역을 시작하겠습니다.
Do you have a chat app?
채팅 앱이 있나요?
I'm sending it to you via chat app.
채팅앱으로 보내드렸습니다.
In such an era,
이런 시기에,
Are there any chat app users out there?
아직도 채팅어플리케이션 사용자가 있나요?
this...
이것...
OK
좋아요.
Provide your chat request number.
채팅 신청 번호를 입력하세요.
However, you just recovered.
그러나 방금 회복되었습니다.
Take it easy.
너무 피곤하지 마십시오.
Don't worry yet.
아직 서두르지 마세요.
Translate slowly.
천천히 번역해 보세요.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
Okay, I'll go first.
알았어, 나 먼저 갈게.
[Kota Jinhai]
[코타진하이]
Yuncheng, would you like a latte or an Americano?
윤청 씨는 라떼를 드릴까요, 아니면 아메리카노를 드릴까요?
as usual.
평소처럼.
A latte without ice and an Americano,
얼음 없이 라떼 한 잔, 그다음 아메리카노 한 잔,
Double espresso, thank you.
더블 에스프레소, 감사합니다.
OK
좋은.
I called Assistant Lin for a while.
나는 잠시 린 조수에게 전화를 걸었다.
of.
의.
[QQ-[Special Attention] Your special friend is online]
[QQ-[특별주의] 당신의 특별한 친구가 온라인에 접속했습니다]
Su Wei'an?
수웨이안?
[Wen Ran] [Invite you to video call]
[웬란] [영상통화를 초대합니다]
Halo, Wei'an.
안녕, 웨이안.
haven't seen you for a long time.
오랜만이에요.
Is there any business?
사업이 있나요?
Is there anything I can't talk to you about?
제가 당신과 대화를 나누기 위해 할 수 없는 일이 있나요 ?
look at yourself,
자신을 살펴보세요.
You can cancel classes any time you want.
원하는대로 학교를 그만 둘 수 있습니다.
You guys have lost touch for three whole years.
당신은 3년 동안 연락이 끊겼어요 .
School friends miss you.
학교 친구들이 당신을 그리워합니다.
I haven't heard from you for a long time
당신의 소식을 들은 지 꽤 오랜 시간이 흘렀습니다.
I am very worried.
나는 정말 걱정을하고 있습니다.
Are you still angry with me?
아직도 나한테 화났어?
So much time has passed,
시간이 너무 많이 흘러서,
I'm not angry with you anymore.
나는 더 이상 당신에게 화를 내지 않습니다.
we are good friends.
우리는 좋은 친구 야.
who are you chatting with?
누구와 채팅하고 있나요?
Yuncheng. look,
윈청. 알다시피,
Who am I chatting with?
나는 누구와 채팅하고 있습니까?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Advanced.
상위.
haven't seen you for a long time.
오랜만이에요.
Consider that you two are already dating.
두 사람이 이미 데이트를 하고 있다고 생각하면 된다 .
happy
행복하다
Thanks.
감사합니다.
Wei An, you...
웨이안, 너...
Where are you?
어디세요?
Why wear patient gown?
왜 환자복을 입고 있나요?
Are you in the hospital?
병원에 있나요?
That's right, Vian.
그렇구나, 웨이안.
Are you OK?
괜찮아요?
I was so excited just now
지금은 너무 흥분해서,
Probably not paying attention.
아마 관심을 기울이지 않을 것입니다.
No.
아니요.
Just a small wound.
단지 작은 상처일 뿐입니다.
Is the wall behind you French?
뒤에 있는 벽이 프랑스산이군요?
Wei An, where are you?
웨이안 씨, 사실 어디 계시나요?
I'm in Lakaya.
나는 라카야에 있어요.
Lakaya?
라카야?
Why did you go there?
왜 거기로 갔나요?
Do you know how dangerous it is there?
거기가 얼마나 위험한지 알아 ?
The news was still reporting last month
지난달에도 뉴스는 계속 보도됐어요
A shootout breaks out in Lakaya.
라카야에서 총격전이 일어났습니다.
Yuncheng,
윈청,
Where are there so many?
어디가 그렇게 많아?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Your idol Dr. Gu is also in Lakaya.
당신의 우상인 구 박사님도 라카야에 계십니다.
Have you met him?
그를 만난 적이 있나요?
What idol?
무슨 아이돌?
Dr. Gu is an extraordinary person.
구 박사는 특별한 사람이다.
Two years in Lakaya
라카야에서 2년
Equivalent to four years of clinical internship in China.
국내에서 4년간의 임상실습에 해당합니다 .
Go to Lakaya to find experience and return to your homeland,
라카야로 가서 경험을 쌓고 고국으로 돌아가라.
You can definitely be promoted to professor.
반드시 교수로 승진할 수 있다.
you can find out
당신은 알아낼 수 있습니다
how
어때?
I am not very sure.
나는 명확하게 모른다.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
This time you have to...
이번에도 거기 있어야 해...
【Assistant Lin】
[린 조수]
Yuncheng,
윈청,
You quickly picked up the phone.
너는 빨리 전화를 받아라.
You get busy first.
먼저 바쁘세요.
Aura.
후광.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I happen to want to ask you for help.
우연히 당신에게 도움을 요청하고 싶습니다.
When I'm in the lab,
제가 연구실에 있을 때,
Her background of false positive chromosomes was severe.
그녀의 위양성 염색체 배경은 심각했습니다.
I remember it wasn't like this before.
예전에는 그렇지 않았던 것으로 기억합니다.
There are many possibilities.
많은 가능성이 있습니다.
How long does it take to separate serum?
혈청 분리 기간은 얼마나 되나요?
half an hour.
반시.
Try adding an hour.
최대 1시간을 추가해 보세요.
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
Back to the lab
다시 실험실로
The teacher once said.
선생님이 한 번 말씀하셨어요.
You see, I've been so busy lately that I've forgotten.
알다시피 요즘 너무 바빠서 잊어버렸어요.
Master never said that.
선생님은 그런 말을 한 적이 없어요.
I said that.
내가 말했어.
[Su Wei'an]
[쑤웨이안]
I still think you were bullied again
아직도 너 또 왕따 당하는 것 같아
By this cunning girl.
이 교활한 소녀에 의해.
In the past, he had
과거에 그는
Make you suffer a lot.
많이 괴로워하게 만듭니다.
With you here, who else can I bully?
너와 함께라면 누구를 억압할 수 있겠니?
You are my only friend in this world.
당신은 이 세상에서 나의 유일한 친구입니다 .
No need to say more.
그렇게 말할 필요는 없습니다.
pain
통증
Sorry, did I hurt your wound?
죄송해요. 제가 상처를 받았나요?
let me see.
어디 보자.
quickly.
빠른.
It's enough.
이미 충분합니다.
Don't expect to touch me.
나를 만질 생각은 하지 마세요.
I...
나...
You really like teasing me, don't you?
너 나 놀리는 걸 정말 좋아하는구나, 그렇지?
Look at what delicious food you brought me .
당신이 나에게 가져온 맛있는 음식을보세요 .
Big dumplings.
큰 만두.
you do not know,
너는 몰랐다,
I'm so bored outside alone
밖에 혼자 있으니 너무 심심해요.
Fortunately, you are by my side.
다행히 당신이 나와 함께 있었어요.
Soon I won't be able to accompany you anymore.
곧 나는 더 이상 당신과 동행할 수 없게 될 것입니다.
On weekends we will go to free therapy
주말에는 무료 진료를 받으러 갔어요
In Labei Village with Dr. Gu.
구 박사와 함께 라베 마을에서.
Rabe Village?
라베 마을?
you're not here,
당신은 거기에 없습니다
So I have to bear it alone
그래서 혼자 들고 다녀야 해요
All translation tasks for the entire medical team.
전체 의료진의 모든 번역 업무를 담당합니다 .
If so, I will accompany you.
그렇다면 제가 동행하겠습니다.
cannot.
캔트.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
당신의 상처는 아직 회복되지 않았습니다.
So heal your wounds here.
그러니 여기서 상처를 잘 치료하세요.
Jiang.
장.
The people of Lakaya Village,
라카야 마을 사람들,
Their French has an accent.
그들의 프랑스어에는 악센트가 있어요.
In addition, there are people who only speak in tongues.
그 외에도 사투리만 구사할 수 있는 사람들이 있다.
You definitely can't handle it alone.
당신 혼자서는 확실히 그것을 감당할 수 없습니다.
This is also true.
그것도 맞습니다.
You can't go either.
당신도 갈 수 없습니다.
What if your wound becomes infected?
상처가 감염되면 어떻게 되나요?
Too dangerous.
너무 위험해요.
I brought gauze and disinfectant.
거즈 와 소독액을 가져왔습니다 .
Besides, if something really happens,
게다가 정말 무슨 일이 있었다면,
Don’t we have the greatest surgeon?
우리에겐 최고의 외과의사가 있지 않나요?
There will be no problem.
문제가 없을 것입니다.
that's right. Dr. Xu had no choice but to provide free treatment.
좋아요. Xu 박사도 무료 치료를 받으러 가야 했습니다 .
Besides, I'm not calm about leaving you either.
게다가 난 널 떠나는 것도 마음이 편하지 않아
alone in hospital
병원에 혼자
OK
좋아요.
Is Wei An still online?
Wei'an은 아직 온라인 상태인가요?
It has been closed since then.
그 이후로 폐쇄되었습니다.
Looks like he's very busy.
그 사람 꽤 바쁜 것 같던데.
So, did he just say
그래서 그 사람이 방금 말했지?
What part of Rakaya is he in?
그는 라카야의 어느 부분에 있나요?
I didn't ask.
나는 묻지 않았다.
I don't know why he would go to such a place.
그리고 그 사람이 왜 그런 곳에 갔는지 모르겠어요 .
Lakaya.
라카야.
Why did it happen in Lakaya?
왜 라카야에 있는 걸까요?
[Su Wei'an]
[쑤웨이안]
(Wei'an)
(웨이안)
(Which area of ​​Lakaya are you in?)
(당신은 라카야의 어느 지역에 있나요?)
(In which hospital?)
(어느 병원에서요?)
Doctor Fang.
팡 박사님.
This French bread is as hard as a rock.
이 프랑스 빵은 돌처럼 단단해요.
I won't eat.
나는 더 이상 먹지 않는다.
I'd better keep it for self-defense.
자기 방어를 위해 보관하는 것이 좋습니다.
Free treatment this time is far away.
이번에 무료 진료를 받는 것은 매우 먼 일입니다.
if you don't eat now
지금 안 먹으면
From now on there will be nothing there.
나중에 거기에는 아무것도 없을 것입니다.
OK
좋아요.
Eat breakfast.
아침을 먹다.
You know you're tired of free therapy,
무료 진료에 지치신 거 아시죠?
I asked the cafeteria aunt to make steamed buns.
나는 식당 이모에게 빵을 만들어달라고 부탁했습니다.
Meat buns.
고기빵.
There are buns.
빵이 있습니다.
wait.
기다리다.
Can everyone please stop eating?
다들 아직 밥 먹지 마세요, 알았죠?
There is such good in the world.
세상에는 이런 좋은 일도 있습니다.
Translator Su is full of careful planning
수 번역가는 꼼꼼한 기획력이 넘친다
Everyone is still invited to enjoy the free breakfast.
여전히 모든 사람 에게 무료 아침 식사를 제공하고 있습니다.
There must be an element of deception in this.
거기에는 속임수가 있어야합니다.
Any tips?
트릭이 있나요?
If you really think you have a trick
정말 비결이 있다고 생각된다면,
You can also give me money.
나에게 돈을 줄 수도 있어요.
One tea egg,
차 계란 하나,
Two steamed buns,
빵 두 개,
A cup of soy milk,
두유 한 잔,
The price is 20 US dollars. It’s not expensive, right?
가격은 20달러인데 과하지 않죠?
I told you, right?
내가 말했지, 그렇지?
Such a breakfast set costs 100 yuan.
이 아침 식사 세트의 가격은 100위안 더 비쌉니다.
What crazy money.
정말 미친 돈이군요.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Who is crazy about money?
돈에 미친 사람은 누구입니까?
You are the one who is crazy about money.
당신은 돈에 미친 사람입니다.
I can't even close my mouth to eat.
먹어도 입이 다물어지지 않습니다.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Our Vian is beautiful and kind.
우리 웨이안은 아름답고 친절해요.
He paid with his own money.
그는 자신의 돈으로 지불했습니다.
However, these buns really shouldn’t be wasted.
하지만 이 빵은 정말 낭비되어서는 안 됩니다.
Overtime pay must be paid for weekend overtime work.
주말 초과근무에 대해서는 초과근무 수당을 지급해야 합니다.
Sooner or later he will be replaced by Dr. Gu.
시간이 지나면 구 박사로 교체될 것입니다 .
OK
좋은.
Gandiya Ganti.
간티 야 간티.
Mali.
마리.
No coriander leaves.
고수 잎이 없습니다.
What?
무엇?
Especially for those who don't have coriander leaves.
특히 고수잎이 없으신 분들은 꼭 드셔보세요 .
How do you know I didn't eat cilantro?
내가 고수를 안 먹었다는 걸 어떻게 알았지 ?
That time when we were eating hot pot,
그때 전골을 먹으면서,
I saw you took out the coriander leaves.
고수 잎을 내놓는 걸 봤어요 .
Even at this age, he is still picky about his food.
벌써 이 정도 크기인데도 여전히 음식에 까다롭습니다.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
Just add a little more medicine.
약을 조금 더 추가하면 됩니다.
what's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
OMG it smells so bad.
맙소사, 냄새가 너무 심해요.
I told you not to drink too much water.
물을 너무 많이 마시지 말라고 했어요 .
You will never get enough of the toilets here .
여기서 화장실을 참을 수는 없습니다 .
Why?
왜?
You stepped on dirt.
당신은 흙을 밟았습니다.
Still talking. Hurry and help clean up.
아직도 얘기하고 있어요. 신속하게 청소를 도와주세요.
It follows.
다음과 같습니다.
Why?
왜?
Kakiku.
Kakiku.
Ayo.
아요.
sit down.
앉아.
A little plan.
작은 계획.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Good seats.
좋은 자리.
What happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
her mother
그녀의 어머니
I haven't been able to speak or move for three months.
3개월 동안 말도 못 하고 움직이지도 못했어요.
He wanted to ask a doctor to come to his house to check it out.
그는 의사에게 집에 와서 확인해 달라고 부탁하고 싶었습니다.
However, you can only go to his house on foot, not by car.
하지만 그의 집까지는 걸어서만 갈 수 있고, 차를 이용할 수는 없습니다.
The kid walked for hours before getting here.
이 아이는 여기 오기까지 몇 시간을 걸어왔습니다.
I beg you, please, my mother.
부탁드립니다. 어머니를 부탁드립니다.
I'll go with you, don't panic.
내가 같이 갈게, 당황하지 마.
You need to treat him first.
먼저 그를 치료하도록 도와주세요.
Doctor Gu, please wait for me.
구박사님, 잠시만 기다려주세요.
I accidentally sprained my foot.
실수로 발을 삐었습니다.
However, I can go with you after a short break.
하지만 잠시 쉬고 나면 당신과 함께 갈 수 있습니다.
enough.
충분 해.
Don't leave.
당신은 가지 않습니다.
This is what your feet look like.
발은 이렇습니다.
It will also take a lot of time for you to go .
가는데 도 시간이 많이 걸릴 거예요.
No, I have to go.
아니요, 가야 해요.
Doctor Gu, please wait for me.
구박사님, 잠시만 기다려주세요.
Jiang Muying.
장무잉.
Don't leave.
당신은 가지 않습니다.
I'll just go alone.
그냥 혼자 갈게요.
How did that happen?
어떻게 그럴 수 있나요?
I will go with you.
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
However, your injury...
하지만, 당신의 부상은...
It's getting better now, don't worry.
더 좋습니다. 걱정하지 마세요.
Is it there?
저기요?
Right there.
그렇죠, 저기요.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Mom, the doctor is here.
어머니, 의사 선생님이 오셨습니다.
You'll be fine.
괜찮아 질거야.
Look at my fingers.
내 손가락 좀 보세요.
Try to hold my fingers.
내 손가락을 잡아보세요.
Hold your fingers.
손가락을 잡아라.
hold onto.
꽉 잡아.
I think these symptoms are
제가 생각하는 증상은,
You can also make a diagnosis.
진단을 내릴 수도 있습니다.
paralyzed,
마비,
Speech disorder.
언어 장애.
most likely
아마도
It's a stroke.
뇌졸중이다.
His condition is already very serious and it should be difficult for him to recover.
이미 상태가 심각해 회복이 어려울 것으로 보인다.
Is there anyone else at home?
집에 다른 사람이 있나요?
I will prescribe medicine later.
나중에 약을 처방하겠습니다.
You tell him first.
당신이 먼저 그에게 말해요.
do this action
이 동작을 해보세요
every day,
매일,
20 kali per set.
세트당 20칼리.
Do three sets every day.
매일 3세트를 하세요.
do this action
이 동작을 해보세요
every day,
매일,
20 kali per set.
세트당 20칼리.
Do three sets every day.
매일 3세트를 하세요.
Legs too
다리도 똑같고
20 kali per set.
세트당 20칼리.
Do three sets every day.
매일 3세트를 하세요.
Legs too
다리도 똑같고
20 reps per set. Do three sets every day.
세트당 20회. 매일 3세트를 하세요.
No need to rush.
서두를 필요가 없습니다.
ensure patient
환자에게 확인하세요.
The joints are sufficiently stretched.
관절을 충분히 늘려 주세요 .
Can't go too fast, okay?
너무 빠르면 안 돼, 알았지?
This way you can help your mother recover.
이렇게 하면 어머니의 회복을 도울 수 있습니다.
Will my mother recover faster if I do this every day?
매일 하면 엄마가 빨리 회복하실 수 있을까요 ?
Mali.
마리.
I believe,
나는 믿는다,
Your mother knows you won't give up
엄마는 네가 포기하지 않는 걸 알아
He will continue to work hard
그 사람도 계속 노력할 거야
and will be restored.
그리고 회복될 것이다.
Take it easy and don't step on rocks.
진정하세요. 돌을 밟지 마세요.
The rocks are slippery, so be careful.
미끄러운 바위, 조심하세요.
Why?
왜?
I'm thinking.
나는 생각 중입니다.
While in the hospital,
병원에 있는 동안,
you keep begging me
너 계속 나한테 빌고 있잖아
Explain the patient's condition honestly .
환자의 상태를 솔직하게 해석합니다.
However, why is it different today?
그런데 오늘은 왜 다를까요?
I clearly know there will be no results
분명히 아무 일도 일어나지 않을 것이라는 것을 알면서,
Why do you have to teach me over and over again?
왜 아직도 나한테 계속 가르쳐주고 있는 거야?
How is the patient's daughter recovering?
환자 딸의 회복 방법은?
Instead of letting them despair and wait for death,
절망 하고 죽음을 기다리게 하기보다는
better one
더 나은
Let’s try it together again.
다시 함께 시도해 보세요.
sometimes,
때때로,
like
사랑
Maybe it can work wonders.
어쩌면 기적을 일으킬 수도 있을 것 같아요.
What if your efforts are fruitless?
노력해도 결과가 없으면 어떻게 되나요?
Is it worth it?
그만한 가치가 있나요?
with loved ones,
사랑하는 사람들과 함께,
Do whatever it takes.
가능한 모든 일을 하십시오.
Come on, let's find a place to take shelter.
자, 피난처를 찾아보자.
There is a cave here,
여기 동굴이 있고,
Take shelter inside.
안으로 대피하세요.
quickly.
빠른.
What now?
지금은 어때?
It rained too much.
비는 너무 무겁다.
We can only wait here first.
먼저 여기서 기다리면 됩니다.
We left after the rain stopped.
우리는 비가 그친 후에 떠났습니다.
That's all.
그게 전부입니다.
No signal?
신호가 없나요?
No.
아무것도 없습니다.
Unable to contact Jiang et al.
Jiang 및 다른 사람들과 연락 할 수 없습니다 .
how?
어떻게?
First light a bonfire to dry the clothes.
먼저 캠프파이어를 켜서 옷을 말리세요.
What’s wrong with you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Maybe my wound was soaked by the rain,
어쩌면 내 상처가 빗물에 노출되었을 수도 있고,
So it's a little uncomfortable.
그래서 좀 아프다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
If this is the case, your wound can easily become infected.
이 경우 상처가 쉽게 감염될 수 있습니다.
let me see.
어디 보자.
unnecessary.
필요 없음.
Later, when I came back, I asked Dr. Xu to examine me.
나중에 돌아온 후 Xu 박사가 나를 검사하게 해주세요.
The rain is too dirty
빗물이 너무 더러워서
Wounds can easily become infected.
상처는 매우 쉽게 감염됩니다.
you...
너...
Don't you feel embarrassed?
부끄럽지 않나요?
Why should I feel embarrassed?
내가 왜 부끄러워해야 합니까?
Aren't doctors just checking patients' wounds?
의사는 환자의 상처를 진찰하는 것만 도와주는 것이 아닌가 ?
I am also studying medicine, is that okay?
나도 의학을 공부하고 있어, 알았지?
Isn't that okay?
그럼 괜찮지 않아?
Let go of your hands.
손을 놓으십시오.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
All I could see was a bit of bandage.
붕대가 조금 보이더군요 .
How do you want me to check your wounds like this ?
이런데 상처를 어떻게 확인하면 좋을까요?
I told you I know how much it hurts.
내가 얼마나 상처받았는지 안다고 말했잖아 .
It really doesn't matter.
정말 괜찮아요.
Let me ask you, Wilson Su.
묻습니다, 소웨이안님.
Am I a doctor or a man?
나는 의사인가 남자인가
in your heart?
당신의 마음에?
certainly...
물론...
Of course it's a doctor.
물론 의사입니다.
If you're a doctor, remove your hands.
의사라면 손을 떼세요.
Because you think I 'm a doctor
당신은 나를 의사로 생각하기 때문에
In the eyes of doctors
의사의 눈에는
patient's body
환자의 신체
Just a set of human organs.
단지 인체 기관의 그룹일 뿐입니다.
There is no difference between men and women.
남성과 여성 사이에는 차이가 없습니다.
man...
남성...
In my eyes you are...
내 눈에 보이는 당신은...
I'm alone.
나는 혼자다.
See for yourself,
직접 보시면,
Already wet from the rain.
이미 빗물에 젖어있습니다.
You still say it doesn't matter.
아직도 괜찮다고 하시네요.
You hold it first.
당신이 먼저 그것을 잡아.
Let me help you change the bandage.
붕대 바꾸는 걸 도와줄게.
Hold on.
잠시만 기다리세요.
already.
이미.
Does it hurt?
그거 아프니?
Thanks.
감사합니다.
Helping you change medications is like fighting a war.
약을 바꾸는 것을 돕는 것은 싸우는 것과 같습니다.
It's getting late.
늦었다.
In fact, when can we leave?
사실, 언제 떠날 수 있나요?
We can't wait any longer.
우리는 더 이상 기다릴 수 없습니다.
Please wait a moment.
다시 기다려 주십시오.
There are two people who haven't come back yet.
아직 돌아오지 못한 두 사람이 있습니다.
Can't wait any longer.
더 이상 기다릴 수 없습니다.
It's raining,
비가 온다,
The road is steep and difficult to pass.
도로는 위험하고 통과하기 어렵습니다.
how about this?
이건 어때?
The driver said he couldn't wait any longer.
운전사는 더 이상 기다릴 수 없다고 말했습니다.
It's very dangerous when it rains
비가 오면 정말 위험해요.
Must leave immediately.
즉시 떠나야 합니다.
how so?
어떻게 그럴 수 있습니까?
The boss hasn't responded to my message yet.
사장님은 아직도 내 메시지에 답장을 하지 않으셨습니다.
The same goes for Wei An.
웨이안도 마찬가지다.
Is there no signal on the mountain?
산에 신호가 없나요?
This is how it should be.
그렇게되어야합니다.
So, how?
그러면 어떻게?
Just wait a little longer. It doesn't matter.
좀 더 기다리세요. 그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
what if
만약
Su dan Gu
수단구
Didn't find the car when you came back?
돌아와서 차를 못 찾았나요?
They must be panicking.
그들은 당황했을 것입니다.
Night is very dangerous.
밤은 매우 위험합니다.
Dr. Xu, let’s put it this way.
이렇게 표현하겠습니다, Xu 박사님.
I'll wait here.
여기서 기다릴게요.
you
너
How about taking everyone back first?
먼저 모두 데려가, 알았지?
I stay here to look for them.
나는 그들을 찾으러 여기에 머물고 있어요.
how can that be possible?
어떻게 그럴 수 있니?
Your leg is hurt.
다리가 다쳤어요.
You go back to the hospital first and rest.
먼저 병원으로 돌아가서 휴식을 취하세요.
That's it, Chiang.
바로 그거야, 장.
I'll wait for them here.
나는 여기서 그들을 기다릴 것이다.
If the boss and Su Weian go back to the hospital
보스와 소웨이안이 다시 병원으로 가게 된다면 ,
You call me.
당신이 나에게 전화.
cannot.
캔트.
My legs are fine.
내 다리는 괜찮아요.
Dr. Xu also checked me.
Xu 박사도 확인을 도와주었습니다.
Just got hit.
방금 맞았어.
besides,
그 외에도
You can't find them alone either .
또한 혼자서는 찾을 수 없습니다 .
I can accompany you.
나는 당신과 동행할 수 있습니다.
What to do if you encounter danger?
위험을 만나면 어떡하지?
As long as you are here, I will not be afraid of danger.
당신과 함께라면 나는 위험을 두려워하지 않습니다.
OK
좋아요.
cannot.
캔트.
leave.
저리 가요.
return!
반품!
Jiang, take your time.
장, 천천히.
The rain has stopped.
비가 그쳤습니다.
That's very good.
좋아요.
It just rained today.
오늘은 방금 비가 내렸습니다.
Now the moon appears.
이제 달이 나타났습니다.
Want to try your luck?
행운을 시험해보고 싶나요?
Maybe we can find the rainbow at night.
어쩌면 밤에 무지개를 찾을 수도 있을 것 같아요 .
Of course I want to.
물론이죠.
However, my luck has not been very good.
그러나 내 운은 늘 나빴다.
I also had bad luck as a child.
내 운도 어렸을 때 나빴다.
However, today we are together and it is possible
하지만 오늘은 우리가 함께라면 가능해요
can complement each other.
서로 보완할 수 있습니다.
Want to go?
가고 싶죠?
Ayo.
아요.
Have you been to Rabe Village?
라베마을에 가보신 적이 있나요?
Why does it feel so familiar?
왜 이렇게 친숙한 느낌이 드나요?
no way.
절대.
However,
하지만,
I can hear the road.
도로 소리가 들립니다.
Hear the road?
길 소리가 들리나요?
It felt like I was trying my luck.
내 행운을 시험하는 것 같았습니다 .
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Don't let your good luck disappear, okay?
행운을 놓치지 마세요 , 알았죠?
Does luck really exist?
행운은 실제로 존재하는가?
Follow the sound of water and you will find the way.
물소리를 따라가면 길을 찾을 수 있다.
I looked it up online.
인터넷에서 찾아봤습니다.
when the moon is full
달이 가득 차면
Below an angle of 42 degrees,
42도 이하의 각도,
When the humidity is high enough,
습도가 충분히 높을 때,
It is possible to see a rainbow at night.
밤에는 무지개를 볼 가능성이 있습니다 .
Today is the full moon.
오늘은 보름달입니다.
There is the sound of water here,
여기 물소리가 들리고,
It has also rained recently.
최근에도 비가 내렸어요.
We keep moving forward,
우리는 계속해서 앞으로 걸어가고,
Maybe you can actually see it.
어쩌면 실제로 볼 수 있을지도 모릅니다.
Ayo.
아요.
slowly.
느리게.
♪Rahasham♪
♪라하시아무♪
♪Luckily I heard all your delirium♪
♪다행히도 당신의 정신 착란 소리를 다 들었어요 ♪
♪I came closer and felt the curve of the corners of your lips♪
♪가까이 다가가서 입술 끝의 곡선을 느꼈어요♪
♪Eternal happiness♪
♪영원한 행복♪
♪ again and again ♪
♪몇번이고 또♪
♪Rahasiaku♪
♪라하시아쿠♪
♪I forgot that I was lonely♪
♪나는 내가 혼자였다는 사실을 잊어버렸어요 ♪
♪I've been waiting for this moment for a long time♪
♪나는 오랫동안 이 순간을 기다려왔습니다♪
♪We will dream about you again...♪
♪우리는 다시 당신에 대한 꿈을 꿀 것입니다… ♪
It turned out to be a nighttime rainbow.
이것은 밤의 무지개라는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
Is this not my misunderstanding?
이건 내 착각이 아니지?
very beautiful.
매우 아름답습니다.
It seems like,
그것은 것 같다,
when the two of us are together
우리 둘이 함께 있을 때,
Our luck is indeed much better.
우리의 행운은 실제로 훨씬 더 좋습니다.
some people's life
평생을 함께하는 사람들이 있어요
It's hard to find such beautiful views.
이만큼 아름다운 풍경을 찾기는 어렵습니다.
However, some people still raised their heads,
그런데 그렇게 고개를 드는 사람들이 있는데,
precious night rainbow
소중한 밤의 무지개
Right in front of you waiting for you.
바로 앞에서 기다리고 있습니다.
I'll give you a priceless heirloom.
나는 당신에게 귀중한 가보를 제공합니다.
I just fished this out of the water.
방금 물에서 이걸 주웠어요.
The myth is that as long as the rainbow appears at night,
신화는 밤 무지개가 나타나는 한,
Then take home the stones you picked up from the water,
그런 다음 물에서 주운 돌을 집으로 가져오십시오 .
God will take away the pain of your illness.
하나님께서는 당신의 질병의 고통을 없애 주실 것입니다 .
Suffering from illness?
질병의 고통?
A great representative professor,
훌륭한 대표교수님,
Folk myths can be told directly.
민속 신화를 직접 말할 수 있습니다.
is this real?
그게 진짜인가요?
You don't believe it, do you?
당신은 그것을 믿지 않습니까?
if you don't believe it
당신이 그것을 믿지 않는다면,
Then just throw it away.
그럼 그냥 버리세요.
No.
하지 않다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
That New Year's kiss,
그 새해의 키스,
Are you in such a hurry to reply?
대답하기가 그렇게 급한가요 ?
You are serious and stiff.
당신은 진지하고 뻣뻣합니다.
You are the best at seducing people.
당신은 유혹을 잘하는 사람이에요.
Which one is the real you?
당신은 어느 쪽이 진짜인가요?
I am serious and strict
나는 진지하고 엄격한 편이다.
Or maybe I’m good at seduction.
아니면 나는 유혹을 잘한다.
Which one do you prefer?
어느 쪽이 더 마음에 드나요?
I know.
알아요.
As long as it's me, you'll like it.
나인 한 당신은 그것을 좋아할 것입니다.
I'm not like that.
나는 그렇지 않습니다.
♪Waiting for the rainy season♪
♪장마를 기다리며♪
♪Looking forward to the next season♪
♪다음 시즌도 기대됩니다♪
♪Padahal kerinduanku♪
♪파다할 케린두안쿠♪
♪You can hear it♪
♪들을 수 있어요♪
♪Signature with your name♪
♪당신의 이름이 적힌 사인♪
♪Trapped on the beach with the moon♪
♪ 달이 뜨는 해변에 좌초되었습니다 ♪
♪Light up the summer night♪
♪여름밤을 밝혀줬어요♪
♪Waiting for the rainy season♪
♪장마를 기다리며♪
♪Looking forward to the next season♪
♪다음 시즌도 기대됩니다♪
♪Remember a fallen leaf♪
♪낙엽을 추억하며♪
♪How to pick up...♪
♪줍는 방법...♪
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
You are the calm one
당신은 차분한 사람입니다.
You are the one who lost control.
당신은 통제 불능의 사람입니다.
You're the weird one.
당신은 이상한 사람입니다.
I like everything.
나는 모든 것을 좋아해.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
내 여자친구가 되고 싶나요?
(Why can't time stop here?)
(여기서는 왜 시간이 멈출 수 없는 걸까요 ?)
(Can I have such happiness?)
(나에게 이런 행복이 허락되는 걸까 ?)
Is it so difficult to answer?
대답하기가 그렇게 어렵나요?
What to answer?
뭐라고 대답해?
answer...
답변...
Answer: you like me
답: 당신은 나를 좋아합니다
And would like to be my girlfriend.
그리고 기꺼이 내 여자친구가 되고 싶어요.
After all, this is not a signature agreeing to emergency action.
결국, 비상 작전에 동의하는 서명은 아닙니다.
You have to give me time to think about it, right?
나한테 생각할 시간을 줘야지 , 그렇지?
[Kota Jinhai]
[코타진하이]
[Su Wei’an: Wei’an, which hospital in Lakaya are you at? 】
[쑤웨이안 : 웨이안 씨, 라카야 어느 병원 에 계시나요 ?]
(Why wear patient gown?)
(왜 환자복을 입고 있나요?)
(Vian, where are you?)
(웨이안 씨, 사실 어디 계시나요?)
I'm in Lakaya.
나는 라카야에 있어요.
Lakaya?
라카야?
Your idol Dr. Gu is also in Lakaya.
당신의 우상인 구 박사님도 라카야에 계십니다.
Have you met him?
그를 만난 적이 있나요?
Assistant Lin, book a flight ticket
린 조수, 비행기표 한 장 예약해줘
Going to Lakaya this Saturday.
이번 토요일에 라카야에 가려고.
[Su Wei’an: Wei’an, which hospital in Lakaya are you at? 】
[쑤웨이안 : 웨이안 씨, 라카야 어느 병원 에 계시나요 ?]
【Outpatient Department】
[외래환자 병동]
The task was successfully completed.
작업은 순조롭게 완료되었습니다.
[HDQ39 Phase II Clinical Trial Report]
[HDQ39 2상 임상시험 보고서]
This is a major breakthrough!
이것은 중대한 돌파구입니다!
It has now entered the third phase of clinical trials.
임상 3상에 진입하게 되었습니다 .
The second level data is so good.
두 번째 수준의 데이터가 너무 좋습니다.
Now I have great confidence
이제는 자신감이 넘쳤어요
For the results of the third phase of experiments.
실험의 세 번째 단계 결과에 대해.
Very good, Professor Wen.
아주 좋아요, 원 교수님.
On behalf of everyone living with Huntington's disease , thank you.
헌팅턴병 환자를 대표하여 감사드립니다.
You give hope to all patients.
모든 환자에게 희망을 드립니다 .
Don’t worry, we’ll be recruiting participants right away.
걱정하지 마세요. 즉시 참가자를 모집하겠습니다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
This project can continue until now,
이 프로젝트는 지금까지 계속될 수 있으며,
Fortunately, I got strong support from Mr. Du.
다행히 Du 씨의 큰 지원이 있었습니다.
Mr. Du, thank you.
두 씨, 감사합니다.
Oh yes, you.
아, 그래, 너.
If you have time, come and have dinner at home.
시간 있으면 집에 와서 먹어요.
OK
좋은.
[HDQ39 Phase II Clinical Trial Report]
[HDQ39 2상 임상시험 보고서]
[Lakaya]
[라카야]
Wait a moment.
잠깐 기다려요.
Why? Can't you walk anymore?
왜? 더 이상 걸을 수 없나요?
Have we lost our way?
우리 길을 잃은 걸까요?
We have a compass,
우리에겐 나침반이 있어요
There is a stream of water and a cluster of stars.
물줄기가 있고 별 무리도 있습니다.
We can definitely get out of here.
우리는 반드시 여기서 나갈 수 있습니다.
What is that sound?
무슨 소리야?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Aren't you very courageous?
배짱이 엄청 큰거 아냐?
Are you already shocked and scared because of such a small thing?
이렇게 작은 일에도 이미 충격과 두려움을 느끼고 계시나요 ?
What do you mean? I'm not surprised by the fear.
무슨 뜻이에요? 나는 두려움에 놀라지 않았습니다.
Be careful!
조심하세요!
How are you?
괜찮으세요?
here.
여기.
Kakiku.
Kakiku.
It hurts, doesn't it?
아프지 않나요?
This is quite painful.
꽤 고통스럽습니다.
Maybe it's just a sprain.
어쩌면 그냥 염좌일 수도 있습니다.
In this case, it shouldn't be a problem with the bones.
그런 경우에는 뼈의 문제가 아니어야 합니다.
Now you can't do much exercise.
이제 운동을 많이 할 수 없습니다 .
Let's make it like this.
이렇게 만들어 보겠습니다.
We are looking for a safe place to wait.
우리는 기다릴 안전한 장소를 찾고 있습니다 .
At least until morning.
적어도 아침까지 기다리세요.
OK
좋은.
Ayo.
아요.
I can do it myself.
내 스스로 할 수있어.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
당신의 상처는 아직 낫지 않았습니다.
slowly.
느리게.
Slowly, yes.
천천히, 그렇죠.
Fang Mingfan, tunggu aku.
Fang Mingfan, 퉁구 아쿠.
This is a mountain road.
이것은 산길입니다.
Are you still afraid?
아직 겁이 나나요?
I'm not afraid.
난 두렵지 않아.
You have to come here.
당신은 여기로 오라고 고집했습니다.
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪